[Music]
Hey Lee, got another shipment?
>> You bet. The best candy mushrooms I know
how to nurture.
Your supplies. Thanks again for the
trade, Lee.
Sure you don't want to come with us?
Meet some people, maybe? Seems pretty
lonely out here.
>> I don't mind being alone. I'm my own
best friend.
[Music]
Awesome. Sounds like new neighbors. It's
been a while.
Welcome friends. Welcome to the land of
Lee.
[Music]
Together we will
find
[Music]
that portal must have messed me up. I'm
seeing double, triple,
five.
>> Follow my lead, no matter how weird it
gets.
>> Hi everybody. I'm Lee. And who are those
guys? That's also me. I'm here and here
and here. I'm all over the place.
>> You're all clones.
>> Nope. Lee is just Lee. I'm one person
who happens to have more than one body.
I'm constantly multitasking.
[Music]
But enough about Lee. Who are you?
Probably four separate individuals with
your own ideas and dreams. Am I right?
>> Yeah, we're ninjoops.
Uh for not introducing ourselves sooner.
I'm Doyle Domagar and this is my little
sister um Wildwire.
>> Huh?
>> Yes, that is exactly my name. Filewire.
It is a normal name and I was given it
at birth so I have had it my whole life.
>> Nice to meet you wilder.
>> Name strong mcool guy. This is my wife
whose name uh I've forgotten.
>> Sorry he's kidding. My husband has an
awful sense of humor. Just awful. My
name is Maya. Maya the cool guy. I love
new people. Nice to meet you, Mrs. Mcool
Guy. Mr. Mcool guy.
>> It's Count Mcool guy. Actually,
>> oh, pardon me. Your countship.
>> Pardon granted. But what happened to us?
The last thing I remember, there was a
big rip in the sky. Then everything went
dark and we woke up here.
>> Don't freak out, okay? But the bad news
is a while back every single realm was
suddenly destroyed in an event called
the merge.
>> That's no one the merge.
>> Wow. Total bummer to hear, Lee.
>> I know, right? But don't you fret.
There's good news. You all must have
been pushed into what's called an
interstitial space bubble. It kept you
safe. Lots of non Lees have returned
from space bubbles, so you'll have many
people to hang out with and we'll never
ever be lonely.
>> Uh, what people
>> you don't mean?
>> Let me show you.
[Music]
>> So, everyone lives in what? An
underground bunker of some kind.
>> Yeah, the fun kind.
>> All this is down here. Who knew? I built
itselves. The hardest part was the
mechanical sun. On the surface, it can
be pretty dreary, but it's always sunny
down here.
[Music]
Friends, an announcement. The community
of Lee has some new neighbors. And you
know what that means?
New neighbor.
[Applause]
>> Buckle up.
[Music]
Perhaps you feel down in the dumps. All
realms destroyed. You've hit a slump,
but cheer up. One haven still has one.
A land where every moment's filled
with fun.
The land of Lee, we got friends galore.
And no one's ever lonely or sad or mad.
In the land of many taverns to explore.
Just tap and swipe and see on my fancy
coffee pad.
Slide into cavern 5 where waters flow
and racing cavern 8. On your mark, set
go. Cavern 12. You can't resist. 17 ft.
Can you handle this?
>> Your friends and family might reemerge
from super spacey powered by a costic
search. But even air they never do. A
jetack race is waving just for you.
Our fake sky gleams so bright and the
sunshine day and night. Get your shades
dragon rides are free. funs our only
currency
before it sends out
love every
time and don't forget our lyrics always
>> um rhyme
[Music]
in the land of all you want
Stay and play at our ice cream mot
[Music]
to rock out on the bells.
[Applause]
[Music]
The air outside will make you sick.
Threats are short. I'm a court and the
haze is crazy thick. Why wander out when
your friends are near? Cuz
stand up comics bring the cheer.
>> Why is he doing this? What's the deal
with the merge? Am I right?
>> Uh cuz his vibe is fierce.
>> No. Why is Lee lying and saying the
merge destroyed the realms and made the
air toxic?
>> Guess he's just trying to keep these
people here for some reason. Time for
the big
>> in the land of look around and see all
your happiness can be found
way
of me. Take a good look around in the
land of at my glorious town. Cuz your
heart will resound with the happiest
sound. Every joy will bound when you go
under the land of me
with me and me and me and me. Cuz me me
and and me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me make me.
[Music]
Um,
thanks for having us. They loved it. The
new neighbors loved it. I knew they
would.
[Music]
[Applause]
You did tell us this place was weird.
>> Ouch.
I think someone could use a teacher.
>> What about two teachers?
>> Good. Your skills are improving, Rayu.
Now try spinjitsu.
>> Remember, focus on your target. You got
this, Frack.
What? All this damage.
>> Apologies, Mr. Froh Hickeyi.
>> We were just trying to train.
>> As the official assistant keeper of the
monastery, I insist you get out so I can
fix all this. But to train Frack, we
need to
>> find some place else to go.
>> Come on, guys. Let's go to the land of
lost things. Plenty of room there. Plus,
Gio's learning to bake, so there might
be some practice cakes laying around.
>> To not upset the bossy frog man, we must
continue elsewhere.
>> Yes, a junkyard might work. Can you lead
us there?
Never thought I'd like a lavaless cave,
but this one's not bad.
>> The whole vibe weirds me out. I can't
believe Lee just gave us this starter
home. We can't all live in ancient
monasteries.
I mean, what's up with that anyway? If
it's a monastery, where are all the
monks? Are you the monks?
>> Welcome, new neighbors.
[Music]
My arm's getting tired from waving at
everyone who waves to us. Why are they
so happy? Does Lee have the mind
control?
>> Nope.
>> How do you know?
>> Back at the administration, we thought
all this happiness was strange, too. So,
we secretly scanned for unlicensed mind
control tech. Nothing. No magical
manipulation, no spirit possession,
nothing strange being chemically added
to the air, water, or food. So, why is
everyone like this? Yeah, as far as we
can tell, everyone here is happy because
they actually like it here. So, the
administration left Lee and the people
down here alone.
>> But the neighbors think they can't
leave. Lee's happy little community is
built on lies.
>> The administration isn't a police force.
They're a bureaucracy. Lying doesn't
require a license or a permit, so they
don't care. In fact, they lied to tons.
Uh, let's focus on the mission. Aaron's
mom and dad. If they've been told
there's no world outside, that would
explain why they never came looking for
Aaron.
>> Why don't we just ask Lee where they
are? He seems friendly enough.
>> That idea wins the stupid award for
stupidest idea ever to stupid.
>> Okay, count the cool guy.
>> If Lee figures out we're not who we say
we are, he'll boot us right out. If
we're going to find Aaron's parents, Lee
can't know about it. So, we act like
good neighbors, split up, and do some
community events, ask questions on the
sly.
>> Just call me Sly Fire.
>> Better spenitsu is half mental. Feel it
in your body and your mind.
Rayu, who did you say owned this
junkyard? Because they might not be too
happy with us.
>> Hi, uh, neighbors. I heard that the
local book club meets here.
>> Yeah, Peron Doyle, right? Join what
promises to be a lively discussion. Oh,
thank you. My friends Jenny and Barry
love to read. I wonder if they're
members of the club.
>> Please hold all other topics until
later. Thank you so much. We're really
jazzed to discuss this week's book now.
>> Between you and Lee,
>> the official autobiography of Lee.
Spoiler. It's really leerrific.
>> Counter point. It's double leerrific.
H you've convinced me. Let's discuss. So
my thoughts is that you know this book
could use a little bit more Lee in this
book.
[Music]
>> Oh hello neighbor. Welcome to the par
part. What's your name?
>> I can't remember. Something dumb. Is it
your birthday or something?
>> Oh I wish. Lee gives everyone free
shoulder rubs on their birthday.
>> So why the party?
>> It's for how great life is. Isn't life
great? It's great.
>> Sure. Sure. But you know who loves
parties? That couple Jenny and Barry.
Seen them around.
>> Never heard of them, but they sound
awesome. Why are you looking for them?
>> What? Who's looking for them? I'm just
being sly in a way that doesn't draw
attention to myself.
>> Oh, okay. Well,
>> well, in that case, I've got a question
for you. How low can you go?
[Music]
>> Not even a challenge. Lower.
I said lower.
>> No one could go that low.
[Music]
Hey, you not impressed with my moves?
>> What? Oh, no. It's It's not you. I can
tell based on how you're acting. You're
not like everyone else here.
>> What? I totally am. Wildfire is my real
name. Dang it. I mean, filed wire. Filed
wire.
>> Well, filed wire. Something tells me you
also think it's weird. Everyone's fine
to just party on and accept what Lee's
telling us. But But
>> it's okay. You're right. I've been
thinking the same thing.
>> I might have proof that Lee's version of
what happened with the merge is a big
lie. Can you meet me later?
Lloyd, being the slyiest clue finder
ever, I got something
>> about Aaron's parents.
>> Not really, but maybe. I found a
neighbor who has some ideas about what's
really going on down here, and he's
ready to expose Lee's secrets.
This is where he said to meet
[Music]
>> Lee.
That's my name. Isn't it a delight to
say? Just rolls off the tongue.
>> Uh, didn't know this was your house.
>> It's not. Just getting it ready for its
next tenant.
>> What happened to the old tenant? Move to
cavern 5. Huge water slide fan.
Everyone's free to move around wherever
they want.
>> I see. Well, we won't keep you.
>> The guy that lived here was going to
blow the whistle on Lee.
>> And Lee just made him disappear.
[Music]
Lee needs the neighbors to not ask
certain questions. But why?
>> Look,
[Music]
why are you snooping around here? Keep
your voice down. Lee has ears
everywhere. You two are new, so you
probably aren't working for him.
>> Who are you?
>> Who I am isn't important. What I am is a
former journalist. I woke up in the land
of Lee about a year ago, so I figured
I'd set up my own community newspaper.
At first, Lee was supportive, but once I
started digging into his story, I found
inconsistencies.
>> Go on.
>> What if the world wasn't really
destroyed? How do we know it's not still
out there? I was supposed to get more
info from the neighbor who lived here,
but now he's gone missing.
The world is still there. We're ninja
from the outside. We're undercover here
to find two people.
>> I'll help you find your people. If
you'll help me tell everyone the truth
about the outside deal,
then follow me. There's something you
need to see.
Hey, my junkyard.
Who did this?
[Music]
>> Rayu. Who's this big jerk?
>> Junkyard owner Creel. I am Rayu's
teacher, Master Ronto. My student and I
are responsible for the condition of
your yard.
>> H. Well, I was hired to demolish all
that junk. I just hadn't gotten around
to it yet cuz it's hard work. And hard
work's not my whole thing. But this is
perfect. Two reckless dragons doing all
the wrecking.
I see. In that case, we can demolish
anything you need as long as we can
continue to train here.
>> Sure works for me.
>> Sometimes things are not as we expect
them to be. Let us resume.
[Music]
Neighborhood Tangle Class.
>> Just keep your eye out for name tags
saying Jenny or Barry.
[Music]
Wow. You two don't need lessons. You're
in perfect sink.
>> No, you're not.
[Music]
I lovely.
I love Lee.
>> That's the guy I told you about.
[Music]
>> He's brainwashing him or something. We
got to get him out of here. No,
you won't be doing that.
>> Gotcha, fakers. Boy, howdy. You are some
bad bad neighbors.
>> What is this, Lee? Look, almost everyone
in my land is a true honest friend who
is just happy to be here.
But every once in a while, some no good
beatnik gets a hairrained idea that your
old pal Lee isn't on the up and up.
Now listen, everything will make sense
when you look at this flower.
Soon you'll forget all your uncharitable
ideas about Lee and we'll be best
friends once again.
[Music]